Summary

Computer Science senior at the University of Wisconsin-Madison driven by an entrepreneurial spirit & passion for building socially conscious technology solutions. 5+ years of experience in full stack development, leadership roles, and a proven capacity to troubleshoot and resolve issues quickly.

Skills

- Python (TensorFlow, Pydicom)
- Java
- Dart
- C
- Golang
- Docker
- GCP, AWS
- ReactJS
- MongoDB, Firestore
- Flutter
- CI/CD
- Git, BitBucket

Accomplishments

- Won 1st at 2019 <u>Diamond Challenge</u> youth entrepreneurship summit (\$11,000 grant)
- 2-time recipient of Dream Big Grant (\$2,000 total)
- Won Alumni Award (\$750) for GroceryMule at UW Transcend business competition
- 1st place for Best Educational App for NHS Tutoring app at MontyHacks hackathon
- Varsity Captain of MHS fencing team (2017-2019)

Education

Bachelor of Science

University of Wisconsin-Madison Computer Science, Expected in 05/2023 Relevant Coursework: Operating Systems, Advanced Algorithms & Data structures, Linear Algebra, Intro to Cryptography • 3.7/4.0 GPA

Undergraduate Teaching Assistant

- TA for Introduction to Cryptography (150+ students) for Prof. Eric Bach
- Held weekly office hours to help students with homework and reinforce class concepts

Coursera Course Certificate

Machine Learning Foundations: A Case Study Approach

- Project-based application of regression, classification, clustering, retrieval & recommender systems, and deep learning
- Grade Achieved: 97.46%

Experience

Dell Technologies - Project Bulldoze

SWE Internship | Austin, TX 05/2022 to 08/2022

- Migrated Dell Cloud platform to the industry standard for cloud resource deployment (Terraform) to incentivize potential customers
- Created several Terraform providers in Golang to automate deployment of virtual machines & networks using Dell Terranova CNS API
- Implemented thorough CI/CD pipeline using Concourse with provider unit testing
- Techstack: Golang, Terraform, Docker

GroceryMule

Co-Founder | Madison, WI

09/2021 to 10/2022

- https://grocerymule.net/
- https://github.com/prafull2001/grocery-mule/tree/main
- A cross-platform mobile app that streamlines shopping for roommates through collaborative shopping lists and automated receipt splitting
- Designed custom non-relational data structures
- Implemented text-recognition receipt scanning using Firebase OCR libraries
- Set up modularized, scalable git-flows for feature rollouts and version control
- · Techstack: Flutter (Dart), Firebase

Dell Technologies - Project Indigo

SWE Internship | Hopkinton, MA

05/2021 to 08/2021

- Project incentivizes reduction of ML computation cost across hundreds of internal teams
- Created Telegraf plugins to enable metrics-driven evaluation of internal ML models
- Implemented thorough unit tests & CI/CD pipeline
- Implemented ARIMA forecasting model to predict Git commit activity to identify optimal maintenance windows for enterprise GitHub servers
- Techstack: Golang, TensorFlow (Python)

Undergraduate Research

Medical Imaging Team Madison, WI 09/2020 to 12/2020

- Creating a deep learning model to identify signs of kidney cancer
- Created 3D CT scan visualizations for better analysis using Microsoft Inner-Eye
- · Techstack: Pydicom, Inner-Eye, Google Colab

MatchMeds

Co-Founder 06/2018 to 08/2020

- Connects low-income patients to clinics providing affordable healthcare options
- Connects patients to clinics ~40% faster than average wait times
- Built the web app using MERN stack (MongoDB, ReactJS, Express, NodeJS), hosted on GCP

Projects

- Unix based shell application written in C
- <u>S.A.V.E. Mobile App</u> streamlines adoption, volunteering, and donating at the S.A.V.E. shelter.
- <u>JUMP3R</u> mobile videogame created using Lua. Reached 10,000+ downloads internationally
- NHS Tutoring App connects MHS students to NHS tutors via private chatrooms and convenient form-based signup